(Amy:)Although, that could just be
my newly defoliated bikini zone.
(Sheldon:)Keep a lookout.
(Sheldon:)This place is swarming
with campus security.
(Sheldon:)They will not hesitate to scold us.
(Amy:)Freaking pigs.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now pull your car into the spot
and let's get out of here.
(Amy:)Wait, I'm leaving my car here?
(Sheldon:)Yes. And be sure
and put on the emergency brake.
It really makes these things tough
to budge.
Before I park, come in the backseat.
I wanna show you something
I had done today.
All right. Color me intrigued.
(Amy:)What do you think?
(Sheldon:)I think you're high on paint fumes.
(Sheldon:)And, boy, that's a lot of Band-Aids.
(Penny:)Okay, Howard's mother is in, like,
every one of your wedding photos.